[{"answer": "The real story behind all those scandals.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Their money, their jobs or my brother's health?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "My feelings are, just as well as the family, the truth is going to come out.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "As we approach the start of this trial, what are your feelings?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "My gut feeling is the fact that Conrad was present during his death, there's a lot of questions to be answered.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Do you think that Conrad Murray was solely responsible for your brother's death?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Well, I think that, first of all, being a cardiologist and not an anesthesiologist, there's a big difference.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "I really don't know but I do know that it's a difference between Demerol and Propofol.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Do you think that's possible?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "I really don't know.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Is Propofol considered by most physicians to be an anesthetic, rather than just a sleeping pill?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "I saw Conrad when I first went to the hospital.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "When did you see Conrad Murray that night in the hospital?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "His behavior, how he was acting.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Did he look guilty?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Did he look concerned?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Did you talk to him?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "He wanted to come in, I guess, and say his -- something to my mother and his condolences or something but I felt uneasy with him.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Did he say anything to any of the family?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "I found out, yes, that he was with Michael.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Did you know that he'd been with Michael that night?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "The surveillance tapes were erased.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Which tapes were erased?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, some of the tapes were erased to the whereabouts who would come in and out during the time, at the house.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "They're all gone?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "They were in the hands of the police department.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Who do you think would erase it?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "We spoke to him not that much during rehearsal.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "And how often did you talk to Michael?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "When -- when \"This Is It\" there was a lot of footage that was taken out that no one saw and because that was the edit before the edit.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Do you know how long he had been given Propofol?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, things that we noticed.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "I mean what is the stuff we didn't see?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "And plus, he's lived all this time doing Demerol and sleeping pills and also, pain pills, but the symptoms from Propofol is like no one knew that he was -- the public didn't know he was complaining about his body.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "-- of knocking somebody out for the purposes of sleep?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I really don't know, but --", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Is there any evidence that you've seen?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Our belief is that we knew he was doing prescription drugs to sleep and pain.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "What is the theory that you think about that?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "No -- no, these are people that were around him.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "The family?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "These are symptoms of that because of the fact that it was administered in him outside of a hospital setting, the person wasn't adequate enough to do this, and the fact that the night that he died, he was -- he had just arranged a $15 million payment on a house.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Are these side effects that you have identified?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Whether it's possible or not, being a doctor, you take an oath.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Is that possible?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "These are people working for AEG, working for him, working for the show.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "These are people working for AEG?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "See, that's the question I have.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "How many of the people directly around him at the time that he died, do you think, are culpable for a form of responsibility for his death?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Because they wanted the show to go on.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Why do you think they didn't?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "No, because the fact that, still, if you have tens of billions of dollars, you still want more but this was an event that was going to put money in everybody's pockets but at the same time, his health was ignored.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "It's not in their interest to raise any alarm bells about his health, is it?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Was it the same kind of body that you would expect?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "To tell you the truth, Piers, it's -- the defense is going to try to paint my brother out to be even most horrible person and he wasn't.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Or this simply just not going to be enough evidence?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Were any of the family attend the trial?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Will you get out?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I'm going to try to be there as much as I can, yes.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I don't feel good about him before I knew him so I'm kind of feel the same way.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "How do you think you'll feel when you see Conrad Murray standing there?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "No, because we've always known that this was just an illusion.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "I mean did you lose peace of mind getting the way you've gotten?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Not so much of the Wacko Jacko.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "And so he played up to a lot of the things, didn't he?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Michael wasn't -- he was very, very much normal.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "How did you feel as his brother?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "My father was tough, but that's still love, because you care to discipline your child and to show them the right path to take.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Your father was a tough guy, though, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Michael --", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "As his big brother, what is the truth about Michael's skin color change over the years?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Was any part of him wishing he wasn't so black?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, I do know that he wanted that.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "How did you see that impact on him as a human being?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "No, but I -- I think he -- he wanted to change the way he looked because he wanted to improve things.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "What was -- what was your view?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "He -- he -- I think in his mind, he had something that he was going after and -- but -- but these things -- once -- once you start, you get caught up into it and then you want to do a little here and there.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "He comes -- is he about -- was he just a perfectionist?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, Martin Bashir needs to be slapped and he never should have been around Michael.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "When you watched that, what did you feel about that interview?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I guess the answer, if I'm putting my media hat back on, because I worked in newspapers at the time of all that, is that it's not normal -- I use that word in, you know, just in a straightforward way -- for a guy of, say, 44, to be sharing a bed with a boy of 12.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "And -- and see, why this -- there's a question for us, why does people in the media want to say the most horrible things about someone, knowing that they have all the right intentions to do good?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "-- or the media --", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "But how do you know that?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I just --", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I just guess -- I don't anybody like that.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "But do you believe that?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Was Michael too innocent for this modern world, do you think?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "He was from the era that -- that we were from.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "You really believe that, that he was just from a different era?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Very, very, very well.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "How are his three children?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "They do, but we don't like it.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Do they -- do they use the Internet and stuff like that?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "They're very much into film.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Do any of them show any signs of wanting to follow in Michael's footsteps as entertainers?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Well, Paris is -- is -- is a star.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Who do you think has the -- the most chance of being a successful actor or actress?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "The good definitely outweighs the bad.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Or does the good that you've enjoyed from all this outweigh the -- the bad?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Michael's done so much good and so many good deeds that he's well protected.", "docId": "110915pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "When this trial starts, if you feel that he's getting unfairly trashed in there, how are you going to deal with that?", "qSentId": 597}]